okay so this is called summation
notation or Sigma notation so it means
we're going to be adding some stuff
together so we're going to take this
we're going to plug in n equals 1 and
then we're going to plug in n equals 2
and then we're going to plug in n equals
3 and we stop when we get to this number
up here so for this first one we plug in
1 for the N for this one we plug in 2
and for this one we plug in 3. 1 squared
is just one so this is all brought down
three times one is three three plus nine
is 12. plus whatever this simplifies to
2 squared is 4 times 3 plus 9. 3 times 4
is 12. 12 plus 9 is 21 plus whatever's
inside here 3 squared is 9 times 3 plus
9. 3 times 9 is 27 plus the 9 is 36. so
now we just want to add up these three
terms two plus one is three plus six is
nine and then one plus two is three plus
three is six so these add up to 69 so
this is equal to 69 and we can put a box
around it nice how exciting